Honey?
蜂蜜？
Have you seen my checkbook?
你见过我的支票簿？
Down stairs in the living room
羽绒服在客厅楼梯
Shh... Darling, are you OK?
嘘......亲爱的，你还好吗？
I'm fine!
我很好！
I'm just gonna take the dog for a walk!
我只是要带狗狗散步！
Nice office
尼斯办公室
Nice family
尼斯家庭
Sorry to disturb you at this time of night, but...
对不起，打扰您了，晚上的这个时候，但是...
we have a little problem.
，我们有一个小问题。
your boss owes me money,
你的老板欠我钱，
a lot of money
很多钱
and I'm here to collect it.
，我在这里收集了。
I'm just  account. I don't know anything.
我只是交代。我什么都不知道。
You don't need to know anything
你不需要知道什么
Except the combination to the safe
除了结合到安全
You do know the combination, yes?
你确实知道的组合，是吗？
Yes.
是
Perfect, please.
完美的，请。
Get in
获取在
Hello my friend, it's Malankov
你好我的朋友，这是Malankov
I came to your office to collect my money
我来到你的办公室收集我的钱
What a disappointment to see it's not here.
真让人失望，看看它不在这里。
But I'm leaving you something here in return.
，但我在这里留下你的回报的东西。
as a reminder
，提醒
I can not wait any longer
，我不能再等了
My best to the family
我的最好的家庭
Sweet.
甜。
Yeah.
呀。
How old?
多大年纪？
No matter how old they are, my friend. They will always be our baby
无论他们多大年纪，我的朋友。他们将永远是我们的宝宝
Ain't that true?
是不是真的？
Come on big guy.
来吧大家伙。
Thank you!
谢谢！
Wow!
哇！
Happy birthday! Dad.
祝你生日快乐！爸爸。
My birthday is not even for 3 days.
我的生日是不是连服3天。
Your always saying I'm so predictable. I wanted to shake
你总是说我太可预见的。我想撼动
things up a bit and make it a little less predictable.
了一点东西，使之少一些预测。
Sorry, come in
对不起，进来
Champagne glasses
香槟酒杯
You know me. Why would I have Champagne glasses?
你知道我。为什么我会有香槟眼镜？
Or a giant stuff panda. I heard that.
还是一个巨大的东西大熊猫。听说。
Inappropriate, huh.
不适当的，呵呵。
Well, I mean...
嗯，我的意思是......
Not if I was 7.
如果我是7。
Well I can I can return it or you can hang on to it
好吧，我可以，我可以归还，也可以挂在它
until you have a 7 year old of your own
，直到你有你自己的的7岁
Not funny.
不好笑。
Hey baby! Babe! Yay!
嘿，宝贝！贝贝！耶！
Hey, look who's here.
嘿，看看谁在这里。
Mr. Mills
先生。米尔斯
Hello Timmy
您好邓肯
How are you? Good, you?
，你怎么样？好，你呢？
You know. Hey! Hi.
你知道。嘿！你好。
Hey, if you guys are having father daughter moment I can really...
嘿，如果你们是有父亲的女儿那一刻我真的可以......
No, no, no, I just dropped by thought I'd do something.
不，不，不，我只是下降想过我会做一些事情。
Unpredictable. Kim is always pointing out how predictable I am.
不可预知的。金总是指出我有多么容易预测。
That's funny coming from her. You wanna talk about predictable.
这很有趣，从她的到来。你想谈谈预测。
I'm not predictable. Come on!
我是不可预测的。加油！
Every single day she goes to the same exact store,
每一天，她去完全相同的店，
right off campus, every morning before class
右键校外，每天早晨上课前
gets the same peach yogurt drink, right? The 4th one from the back,
得到相同的桃子酸奶饮料，对不对？从后面的第4 1，
not the 5th one, not the 3rd one, right? Stop.
不是5号的，而不是3的，对不对？停下来。
Cause it's still cold.
因为它仍然寒冷。
I know. I would do exactly the same thing
我知道。我会做同样的事情
Yeah, the OCD gene
呀，OCD基因
So, whats with the bubbly?
那么，什么与气泡？
Pre-birthday celebration -Nice
预生日庆典 - 尼斯
If you don't mind, I think it's just a little early to pop open a bottle.
如果你不介意的话，我认为这只是一个小初流行开了一瓶。
Yeah. Yeah, no problem. I'll put it in the fridge.
呀。是啊，没问题。我把它放在冰箱里。
What was that?
那是什么？
Well, I'll leave you two
好吧，我会离开你们两个
Dad font...
爸爸字体...
You don't have to take it. Now I feel bad.
你不必把它。现在我感觉不好。
Yeah, you should feel bad. I'll exchange
是啊，你应该感觉不好。我会换
it for something more predictable.
它的东西更容易预测。
Love you. Take it easy, Jimmy. -Alright!
爱你。别紧张，吉米。 -Alright！
Hey, how you doing? Is something wrong?
嗨，你好吗？是什么问题？
Nothing -You sure, babe?
没事 - 你肯定的是，贝贝？
How'd it go?
你怎么样？
Great, fantastic. It couldn't have gone better
伟大的，太棒了。它不可能更好了
The panda was not a hit, i take it.
熊猫是不是一个打击，我把它。
Careful what you say. He's sitting right next to me
小心你说的话。他坐在我旁边的
When did she grow up, Lenore?
她什么时候长大了，勒诺？
I know
我知道
It goes so fast. All of it
它会这么快。所有这一切都
Where are you?
你在哪里？
just going home. Make a little dinner
刚准备回家。赚点吃饭
If you'd like to join us. Us? Me and the panda
如果你想加入我们的行列。我们呢？我和熊猫
I'll uh...
我会呃...
I'll take a rain check on that. If thats OK with you?
我要在一个下雨的检查。如果多数民众赞成OK呀？
And the panda
和熊猫
That's fine by us
这很好由我们
I'll see ya.
我来看看你。
See ya
再见
I know what your thinking
我知道你的想法
Keep it to yourself
保持它自己
Hey -Lenny
嘿-Lenny
You changed your mind -Yeah
你改变主意是啊
You left the door open. -Come on in
您敞开了大门。在 -COMe上
OK
OK
I'm not intruding or anything.
我没有入侵或任何东西。
Of course your not, I was just preparing dinner, drink?
当然你不是，我只是在准备晚餐，喝？
Yes, please.
是的，请。
Thanks for coming over
感谢光临
Cheers -Cheers
干杯-Cheers
You look stressed. -Yeah. Why?
你看上去强调。是啊。为什么呢？
Stuart and I...
斯图尔特和我...
we've tried everything. Therapy, counseling, together, separately
，我们已经竭尽所能。治疗，辅导，同时，分别
He wants it to work. He really does.
他想它的工作。他确实做到了。
And you? -I know I'm hurting him
，你呢？ - 我知道我伤害了他
I just don't feeling anything anymore.
我只是不感觉什么了。
I hate that. I hate not feeling. I hate going through the motions.
我讨厌这样。我讨厌不舒服。我讨厌走过场。
They only thing I feel is trapped.
他们唯一让我觉得被困住了。
I have the worst taste in men. -Thanks
我在男人最糟糕的味道。 - 谢谢
Oh my God!
哦，我的上帝！
I wasn't talking about you. Oh God, I'm sorry.
我不是说你。哦，上帝，对不起。
Its OK.
其确定。
Do you know what I fantasize about?
不要你知道我的幻想？
I'm afraid to ask
我怕问
Us
我们
Yeah?
呀？
Right after the guilt comes roaring in, I feel like such a shit
右后内疚咆哮而来的，我觉得像这样的狗屎
Does that make me a bad person? Being married
这是否使我成为一个坏人吗？结婚
to one man, fantasizing about another?
到一个人，幻想着另一种？
Confused, maybe. Bad, no
迷茫，也许。不好，没有
You must think I'm crazy
你一定以为我疯了
If you are Lenny, you're not the only one
如果你是莱尼，你不是唯一一个
Lenny
莱尼
I'm sorry. -No
对不起。 -No
This lead that you are apologizing. It's not that I don't want to, believe me
这导致您道歉。这并不是说我不想，相信我
But until you and Stuart clear up your situation,
，但直到你和斯图尔特清理你的情况，
I think it would do more harm than good
，我认为它会做的比好更多的伤害
For all of us
对于我们所有人
Why do you have to be so damn honorable
你为什么要这么该死的光荣
Believe me, right now I wish I weren't
相信我，现在我希望我是不是
I'm gonna go. -Wait!
我要去。 -Wait！
Here
这里
I'm going out of town in a couple of days, for a month, on a job
我要出城了几天，一个月，对工作
If you ever feel you need to go to someplace just to be by yourself
如果你觉得你需要去的地方只是为了自己
Use it
使用它
Thank you
谢谢
Will the rest of you gentlemen please.
请问你休息先生们，请。
Seriously, it's money. It'll be fun.
严重的是，它的钱。这将很有趣。
I know. I can't go
我知道。我不能去
It's a four man job. We can't do it without you
这是一个4人工作。没有你，我们不能这样做
I know, I know, but a couple of things have come up and
我知道，我知道，但有几样事情都拿出了和
I'm not comfortable being away for a month right now.
我不舒服暂时离开了一个月现在。
Kim?
金？
It's not Kim.
这不是金。
Man, you got to let this go. Lenore is a grown women she can take care of herself.
男人，你得让这个去。勒诺是一个成长的女性，她能照顾好自己。
Your not her husband any longer.
您没有丈夫的任何更长的时间。
But she is my friend
，但她是我的朋友
I think you better talk to somebody about this.
我想你最好跟别人约了。
A shrink maybe?
一个收缩可能？
Why would I go to a shrink when I got you guys?
为什么我会去收缩时，我得到了你们？
Well there's a good point
那么有一个好点的
Could somebody drop the flag stick?
可能有人丢弃标志贴？
Hey Kim, what's up?
嘿金，这是怎么回事？
-You want me to take it out? -If you wouldn't mind.
- 你想让我把它拿出来？ - 如果你不介意的话。
Sure! When?
当然！当？
-Oh come on. -OK, baby.
- 哦来吧。 -OK，宝贝。
Come on!
加油！
OK, the big moment.
OK，重大时刻的到来。
-That's a good... -Oh!
- 那是一个很好的......  - 哦！
Well, this is an unexpected treat
那么，这是一个意想不到的治疗
Yeah, I um...need some advice
是啊，我嗯...需要一些建议
OK, shoot.
OK，拍摄。
So, its um...
因此，其嗯...
I guess its not something I was really planning on here or even thought about.
我想它不是我真的打算在这里甚至想过。
ever.
如初。
Anyway, I just wanted your advice.
反正，我只是想你的建议。
I'm flattered.
我受宠若惊。
Wow.
哇。
Poor lady.
可怜的女人。
That it going to be serious trouble in a few years. You mark my words.
这也将是在未来几年内严重的麻烦。你记住我的话。
So, what was it you wanted to ask?
那么，是什么，你要问？
Um...
嗯......
Um...Puppy.
嗯......小狗。
A puppy?
一只小狗？
Yeah, I was thinking about getting a puppy.
是啊，我是想获得一只小狗。
-From where? -Um, my friend found one behind a building.
- 从哪里呢？ -um，我的朋友发现了一个建筑物的后面。
-Uh huh -We were trying to find it a home.
-Uh吧 - 我们正试图找到一个家。
You know we put it on Facebook, but nobody claimed it yet, so.
你知道，我们把它在Facebook上，但没有人声称它，所以，
Wanna know what I think?
想知道我怎么想？
Yeah.
呀。
I mean its alot of work, alot of responsibility,
我的意思是它的大量的工作，责任很多，
and with your lifestyle and your going to college
，并与你的生活方式和你去上大学，
But a puppy you have to be there all the time.
但是一只小狗，你必须在那里所有的时间。
Feed it, walk it. No different than having a kid
喂养它，它走。没有比拥有一个孩子不同的
-Have you had a chance to look at the menu? -Not yet, Annie.
- 具备你有机会看看菜单吗？ - 不还，安妮。
What will I have?
什么会我？
-Stuart. -Hey Brian.
-Stuart。 - 嘿布莱恩。
-What are you doing here? -Um...
- 什么，你在这里做什么？ -um ...
Everything alright? -Yeah, its fine, its fine.
一切都还好吗？是啊，它的精细，它的罚款。
Can I talk to you inside?
我能和你谈谈里面？
Yeah, yeah, sure. I was just making some coffee.
是啊，是啊，肯定的。我只是做了一些咖啡。
-Milk? Sugar? -Um, both please.
-Milk？糖吗？ -um，无论是请。
OK.
确定。
-Milk, cold or hot? -Uh...
-Milk，或冷或热？ -Uh ...
Hot.
热。
So, how's business?
那么，怎样的商业？
Oh, you know. Some days good. Some days great.
呵呵，你知道的。有些日子好。有些日子太好了。
Yeah.
呀。
-One sugar or two? -Two, please.
多功能一体糖还是两个？ - 两个，请。
-Here we go. -Thanks.
，尤其是圆形才好。 - 谢谢。
Um...
嗯......
I'm sorry to bother you this late, but I thought it was more um...
对不起，打扰你这么晚，但我认为这是更嗯...
respectful to say what I have to say you. Face to face. Man to man, so to speak.
恭敬的说什么我不得不说你。面对面。人盯人，可以这么说。
Listen, I know that Lenore has
听着，我知道勒诺有
she's spoken to you about the problems that we've been having.
她跟你们说，我们一直有这些问题。
um
UM
Your a good guy, Brian. I like you. Your a respectful guy
你是个好人，布莱恩。我喜欢你。你尊重的人
And listen, I'm not accusing you of anything. But
听着，我没有指责任何你。但是，
Lenore and I If your marriage is gonna work,
勒诺，我如果结婚是要去工作，
that can't happen with you in between us.
，可以不跟你发生在我们之间。
Stuart, there's nothing between Lenore and I other than we share Kim.
斯图尔特，​​还有勒诺和我之间没有任何东西比我们分享金等。
I didn't say there was.
我没有说有。
You know obviously you share a daughter and
你明明知道你分享一个女儿和
your tried to be the best father that you can.
你想成为最好的父亲，你可以。
Under the circumstances.
在这种情况下，
And part of that means the two of you talking and staying in touch.
而这部分意味着你们两个谈话和保持联系。
But, I still want you to stop seeing my wife.
不过，我还是希望你停止看到我的妻子。
Until we sort things out.
直到我们理清头绪。
-Does she know your here?
-Does她知道你在这里？
Doesn't matter if she does or if she doesn't. That's not the point.
如果她不还是不要紧，如果她不。这不是问题的关键。
I'm asking you to stop seeing my wife. Can you do that?
我要问你停下来看到我的妻子。你能做到吗？
I can do that.
我能做到这一点。
Wow, that's great. Thank you.
哇，这是伟大的。谢谢你。
You know I got to go to Vegas tonight some business meeting tomorrow.
你知道我必须去拉斯维加斯今晚一些商务会议的明天。
I really don't want to be worrying about
我真的不希望被担心
-you know -Yeah.
- 你知道 - 是啊。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I really appreciate it.
我真的很感激。
Need to see you. Urgent. Bagels.
需要见你。迫切。面包圈。
I'll have four bagels and some cream cheese, please.
我有四个百吉饼和一些奶酪，请。
OK, be careful they're really hot.
OK，小心他们是真热。
Thanks.
感谢。
Have a good day.
有一个好的一天。
Take care. -Thanks.
小心。 - 谢谢。
Hello?
喂？
Lenny?
莱尼？
Jesus Christ! Lenny, wake up!
耶稣基督！莱尼，醒了！
Come on, come on, come on! Lenny!
来吧，来吧，来吧！莱尼！
Freeze! Don't move!
不许动！别动！
-Step away from the knife!
-Step远离刀！
-Get your hands up! -Sir, back away now!
- 获得你的手！ -SiR，往回走了！
-I didn't do this. -Get your hands up, now!
- 我没有做到这一点。 -GET你的双手，现在！
Slowly!
慢！
-Get your hands up! -You got to listen to me!
- 获得你的手！ - 你得听我的！
-One the floor, now! -Listen to me!
多功能一体机楼，现在！ - 听我说！
-Down on the floor, now!
-Down在地板上，现在！ - 听我说！
On your knees!
在你的膝盖！
Now!
现在！
Put your hands up!
把你的手了！
Hands up!
举起手来！
Higher! Higher!
高！更高！
I didn't do this.
我没有做到这一点。
Shit! Over there!
妈的！那边！
Get em!
找他们！
Come on, he's heading west!
来吧，他向西！
Stop!
停止！
Get inside. I'll be back.
进入。我会回来的。
Police, freeze!
警察，不许动！
-Door is sealed. I just saw him inside. -Shit!
- 门是密封的。只见他进去。 -Shit！
Clear! Moving in!
清除！朝着！
You see him anywhere?
你看他的任何地方？
He disappeared.
，他就消失了。
God damn it, he's gone.
他妈的，他走了。
This is 103, suspects gone.
这是103，犯罪嫌疑人走了。
-Yeah -Kim, Its dad.
-Yeah -Kim，它的爸爸。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
I'm at mom's. Looking for my yellow sweater.
我在妈妈的。寻找我的黄​​毛衣。
Are you alone?
你是一个人吗？
Stuarts in Vegas, why?
在拉斯维加斯斯图亚特王朝，为什么？
I have something to tell you.
我有件事要告诉你。
Dad?
爸爸？
Dad, whats wrong?
爸爸，什么是错？
Something terrible has happened and I wanted you to hear it from me first.
可怕的事情发生了，我想你听到它从我第一。
Your mom...
你妈妈......
She's dead.
，她已经死了。
Someone murdered her.
有人谋杀了她。
In my apartment.
在我的公寓。
It looks like I did it. I don't know why, I don't know who, but I'm gonna find out.
它看起来像我做到了。我不知道为什么，我不知道是谁，但我会找到答案。
Listen carefully, Kim.
仔细听，金。
No matter what anyone says, don't trust them.
不管别人怎么说，不要相信他们。
No.
无。
-You hear? -I'll find a way to contact you.
- 你听到了吗？ -I'll找到一个方法来与您联系。
-Dad? -Try to be strong.
-Dad？ -Try要坚强。
-I love you.
-Dad？ -I爱你。
Wait!
等待！
You need to check this out, alright?
你需要检查了这一点，好吗？
Sargent Dotzler, suspect name is Brian Mills.
萨金特多兹勒，犯罪嫌疑人的名字叫布莱恩·米尔斯。
His?
他？
His.
他。
Not his.
不是他的。
Your officers happen to see him because?
您人员碰巧看到他，因为？
We got this call. Came in reported a women
我们得到了这个电话。排在报道一个女性
screaming, "He's killing me, he's killing me"
尖叫，“他的杀了我，他的杀了我”
Her name is Lenore St. john.
她的名字是勒诺圣约翰。
We sent a card to her address that was listed on her license.
我们送一张卡片给她被列在她的执照地址。
Her daughter was there but her husband was in Las Vegas on some business
她的女儿在那里，但她的丈夫是在拉斯维加斯的一些商业
He's, uh, taking the first flight home.
他，呃，采取的第一个飞行家。
Any witnesses?
任何证人？
The cameras didn't see anything at all.
的摄像头并没有看到任何东西。
Call came from an unlisted number
呼叫来自一个非上市数量
I'll had them checked out the cells as well
我有他们签出的细胞以及
Download both the phones. Encrypt the data.
下载两个手机。加密数据。
I wanna know when these two people...
我想知道，当这两种人...
spoke, text, emailed. Every form of communication.
讲话，文本，电子邮件发送。通信的各种形式。
Date, times, durations of calls.
日期，时间，持续时间通话。
Lets bag this.
让包包了。
Take that. Bag it up.
拍摄的。包起来。
What's wrong?
什么是错的？
Good.
好。
Right now this is still a very active crime scene.
现在这仍然是一个非常活跃的犯罪现场。
investigators have been here, on the scene, all morning but so far,
研究人员一直在这里，在现场看到，整个上午，但到目前为止，
police have not told us what happened inside the apartment
警方还没有告诉我们发生了什么公寓里面
where, earlier this morning, a women's body was discovered.
其中，今天上午早些时候，一个妇女的尸体被发现。
Brian Mill's is the owner of the apartment and the ex-husband of the deceased.
布赖恩·密尔的是公寓和前夫死者的所有者。
-Who's this? -It's me.
- 谁的呢？ - 它是我。
-Your on the news - i didn't do it, Sam.
- 您的新闻 - 我没有做到这一点，萨姆
Obviously you didn't do it. Are you alright?
显然，你没有做到这一点。你还好吗？
I'm going down the rabbit hole.
我要下去了兔子洞。
-The code still the same? -Yeah, yeah, its still the same.
-The代码仍然是一样的吗？是啊，是啊，它仍然是相同的。
-I'll be in touch. -Be careful.
-I'll保持联系。 -be小心。
So this is the area we lost him, sir.
所以，这就是我们失去了他的区域，先生。
It got fetched.
它有牵强。
Uh, thats the gun that he took off one of our officers, sir.
呃，那他脱下我们的人员之一枪，先生。
He had a gun?
，他有枪？
And he didn't fire at you?
他没有开火吗？
No, sir.
不，先生。
And the Helicopters? So whats their view?
而直升机？所以，什么他们认为？
Choppers didn't see anything, Sargent.
砍刀什么也没看见，萨金特。
I know he's good.
，我知道他的好。
But
，但
Vanish into thin air?
成为泡影？
Lets move the truck.
让移动的卡车。
Do you know why your wife went to visit Mr. Mills?
你知道为什么你的妻子去探望米尔斯先生？
No, I don't know.
不，我不知道。
You know there relationship was mostly centered around their daughter.
你知道有关系，主要是围绕着他们的女儿。
Um, but I think that he wanted more than friendship
嗯，不过我认为他想超过友谊
I asked her to speak to him and tell him that she should stop bothering her about it
我要她跟他说话，告诉他说，她应该停止打扰她吧
So you think that's what she was doing over there?
所以，你认为这是她在做什么了呢？
-I don't know. -What are you doing?font
- 我不知道。 - 什么你在干什么？字体
Stuart? Why are they going through my mom's stuff?
斯图亚特？为什么他们会通过我妈妈的东西？
Hey Kim.
嘿金。
Mrs. St. John.
夫人。圣约翰。
-Franck Dotzler. -Mills.
-Franck多兹勒。 -Mills。
My name is Mills.
我的名字是米尔斯。
Can I just have for a few minutes of your time. Ask you a few questions.
我可以只对你几分钟的时间。问你几个问题。
Why aren't you out there trying to find out who did this?
为什么不是你在那里试图找出是谁做的？
Instead of standing around going through our home.
而不是站在一旁经过我们的家。
We can't be bound through looking
我们无法通过寻找约束
But in order for me to get a full picture,
，但为了让我得到一个全面的了解，
I have to ask questions of him and questions of you.
我要问你他和质疑的问题。
My mom went to see my dad. I don't know why.
我妈去看我爸。我不知道为什么。
Probably to talk about me.
大概谈论我。
Look, there's just
看，但只是
he didn't do it!
，他并没有这样做！
He just didn't. He didn't do it. There's no way on earth he would
他只是没有。他并没有这样做。有地球上没有办法，他会
Come on, Kim.
来吧，金。
Just don't!
只是不要！
He loved her.
他爱她。
That's all I know.
这是我所知道的。
Please.
请
That's mine. That's not even hers.
这是我的。这甚至不是她的。
Excuse me.
对不起。
-God! -Come on, lets get you home.
- 神！ -COMe上，让你带回家。
If something comes to mind, anything at all.
如果事情想到的，什么都没有。
You know it might not be anything, um...
你知道这可能不是什么，嗯...
You know what happen in Paris and Istanbul,
你知道什么是发生在巴黎和伊斯坦布尔，
a couple of years ago, were Bryan saved his family.
几年前，分别为布莱恩救了他的家人。
Sure, you that's connected to this?
当然，您在连接到这一点？
You know, I never really wanted to know all the details. But,
你知道，我从来没有真正想知道所有的细节。但是，
A lot of people ended up dead and now this?
很多人最终死了，现在呢？
So what your telling me is...
那么，你告诉我是...
I'm dealing with a very dangerous man.
我处理一个非常危险的人物。
No!
不行！
Brian's not dangerous.
布莱恩不是危险的。
The world he lives in is.
，他生活在这个世界。
He loves his family.
他爱他的家人。
But he has a lot of enemies.
，但他有很多敌人。
I see.
我明白了。
Bring him into room 3.
带他进入房间3。
Garcia, will uh, get you back home.
加西亚，将呃，让你回家。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
This guy is a ghost.
这家伙是一个幽灵。
he's in the army
他在军队
he joins special forces.
他加入特种部队。
He's good.
，他是很好的。
No service records. No discharge. Nothing! Nothing!
无服务记录。无分泌物。没事！没事！
Sounds like spy shit to me.
听起来像是间谍狗屎给我。
And until we have another suspect, he's our man.
而直到我们有另一名嫌疑人，他是我们的人。
So here's our best way of finding him.
因此，这里是我们最好找到他的方式。
His daughter with the deceased.
他的女儿与死者。
The husband says that he is really close to her.
的丈夫说，他是真正贴近她。
Devoted to her.
倾注了她。
So lets keep a close watch on her.
所以让我们密切关注着她。
Where she goes, who she calls, who she talks to.
她去哪里，她叫谁，谁她会谈。
Lets not screw this up, OK?
让不搞砸了，OK？
So this is gonna be our best shot at finding him.
所以这会是在寻找他我们最好的拍摄。
Do we have the deceased car?
我们是否有死者的车？
Yeah, that just came in.
是啊，这只是走了进来。
- There it is still. -Alright.
- 在那里，它仍然是。 -Alright。
Garcia. Smith.
加西亚。史密斯。
Go sweep the car. GPS download it see where it went and when.
去扫车。 GPS下载它看到它去当。
see if they correlate.
看他们是否相关。
See if we can find out what's going on.
看看我们是否可以找出发生了什么事情。
Just came in, its a nerves.
刚进来的时候，它是一种神经。
Lets go then.
让去了。
Follow me.
跟我来。
So, what's this about?
那么，这是什么呢？
-Some guy offed his ex. -Allegedly
- 某些人offed方案前妻。 -Allegedly
Right.
右键。
Allegedly
据称
-He didn't do her in the car, did he? -Nah, at his house.
- 他没有做她的车，是吗？ -Nah，在他家。
Good, I hate to clean it up after.
好，我讨厌之后把它清理干净。
Blood.
血。
pieces of flesh and shit that is disgusting.
肉和狗屎这是令人厌恶的部分。
Which GPS you want done first?
GPS哪个你想先做些什么？
His.
他。
-His first. -Right over her.
-His第一。 - 右过她。
What the hell were you doing all the way out there, Leonore.
什么是地狱，你在做所有的出路在那里，列奥诺拉。
Excuse me.
对不起。
Inspector Malry LAPD.
督察Malry LAPD。
We're following up on a missing person investigation.
我们正在对失踪人员调查跟进。
Was wondering if you've seen this women?
想知道，如果你已经看到了这个女人？
-Nope. -
-Nope。 -
-She was her about 10pm last night. -I was here then.
- 她是她晚上10点左右昨晚。 -I在这里呢。
I didn't see her.
我没看到她。
Didn't see hardly nobody.
没看到几乎没有人。
not exactly a best selling destination if you know what I mean.
，如果你明白我的意思不完全是一个最畅销的目的。
Hey, Sarah.
嘿，莎拉。
Excuse me, duty calls.
对不起，值班电话。
Amanda
阿曼达
Excuse me.
对不起。
Inspector Malry LAPD.
督察Malry LAPD。
Are these security cameras operative or are they just there for show?
难道这些监控摄像头手术或者是他们只是在那里作秀？
Yeah they work.
是啊，他们的工作。
Follow me.
跟我来。
You have the tape from yesterday?
您已经从昨天？磁带
No I wasn't here. The other guy was.
不，我不是在这里。其他人了。
If someone was here, it'd be on there.
如果有人在这里，这将会是在那里。
Just push that button for playback.
只需按下该按钮进行播放。
I'm just gonna stay here while you look at that.
我只是要去住在这里，而你看那个。
you have problems with this system?
你有问题，这个系统？
It breaks down sometimes. They keep saying their going to replace it.
它打破了，有时。他们一直说自己要去取代它。
Excuse me.
对不起。
Have you seen this women?
你有没有见过这个女人吗？
-You fellows should get more coordinated. -Coordinated?
- 你的家伙应该得到更加协调。 -Coordinated？
What you mean? Like color coordinated?
什么意思？喜欢的颜色协调？
No, like one of your guys was just in here asking the same thing.
不一样，你的球员之一，只是在这里问同样的事情。
One of our guys?
我们的一个家伙？
Yeah.
呀。
-Him? -Yeah.
谦诚？是啊。
Him.
他。
Took off to the gas station.
起飞的加油站。
Shh
嘘
Freeze!
不许动！
Mr. Mills!
先生。米尔斯！
Step out buddy!
走出哥们！
Get up out of here!
起床离开这里！
Freeze!
不许动！
Stop what our doing, Mr. Mills. Step away from the desk!
停止什么我们做什么，米尔斯先生。从办公桌一步之遥！
-Back away from that desk. -Step away from that desk!
- 后远离办公桌。从办公桌-Step了！
I'll shoot you!
我就开枪了！
Step away from the God Damn desk, now!
从该死的办公桌一步之遥，现在​​！
Step away one step from the desk!
步距办公桌一步！
Just keep your hands were we can see them.
只要保持你的双手，我们可以看到它们。
Stay perfectly still!
保持完全静止！
You know the drill.
你知道该怎么做。
Anything you say can and will be used against you in the court of law.
你说什么可以和将在公堂上被用来对付你。
You have the right to an attorney.
您有律师的权利。
If you have one present during questioning...
如果您在讯问过程有一个礼物...
Garcia and smith, they got him.
加西亚和史密斯，他们得到了他。
-He's here? -Yeah, just picked him up.
- 他在这里？是啊，刚把他抱起来。
Easy peasy
易peasy
If he was a pro, like you said. He wasn't on his game today.
如果他是一个职业球员，像你说的。他是不是对他今天的比赛。
-He's playing you. -What are you talking about?
- 他在玩你。 - 什么是你在说什么？
-Where is he? Where is he? -He's back in Phillips care, why?
-where是他？他在哪里？ - 他的背部在菲利普斯照顾，为什么？
-Stop the cars! -What!?
-Stop的汽车！ - 什么！？
Now!
现在！
Aw, come on.
噢，来吧。
-Phillips. -Yeah.
-Phillips。是啊。
Our boss has got a hair up his ass about something.
我们的老板已经有了一个发了他的屁股的东西。
Just keep an eye on this guy, alright?
只要保持这个家伙的眼睛，好吗？
Yeah, OK.
呀，OK。
They think we're idiots. It's unbelievable.
他们以为我们是白痴。这是令人难以置信。
-He acts like I never done this before. -He's just being Dotzler
- 他就像我从来没有这样做过。 - 他只是被Dotzler向您
Nah, you know what it is? He's a control freak.
不，你知道是什么吗？他是个控制狂。
If he's not doing it himself, he's not happy.
如果他不这样做他自己，他高兴不起来。
Keep driving!
保持驾驶！
Phillips!
菲利普斯！
Come on!
加油！
Oh my God! What the hell is he doing!?
哦，我的上帝！这到底是他在做什么！？
Pull it over!
拉过来！
Back it up!
回吧！
Get out of the car!
下车的！
Drive!
驾驶！
Drive, Come on!
驱动器，加油！
Now move!
现在移动！
Radio!
收音机！
Cell phone!
手机！
-This is gonna end bad for you. -Don't be such a pessimist
- 这是会结束对你不好。 - 不要出现这样的悲观主义者
Connecting to LAPD computer files
连接到电脑LAPD文件
Calling unit a code 10-29 on police con number 706
电话单元警务CON数706 代码10-29
Number 706.
号码706。
Suspect in sight!
犯罪嫌疑人的视线！
Move! Move! Move!
移动！感动！动了！
LAPD! Freeze!
LAPD！不许动！
Send some back up, now!
发送一些回去了，现在！
Dotzler
多兹勒
By now I'm sure you know who I am.
到现在我敢肯定，你知道我是谁。
You know what I'm capable of.
你知道我的能力。
CIA operative. 66' 67' what?
CIA工作。 66'67'是什么？
All you have to know is I'm innocent.
所有你必须​​知道的是我是无辜的。
Give me 2 days and I can prove it. I can find out who did it.
给我2天，我可以证明这一点。我可以找出是谁做的。
You may very well be innocent, Mr. Mills.
你很可能是无辜的，米尔斯先生。
But that's the courts job to decide, not mine.
但是，这是法院的工作来决定，不是我的。
My job is to bring you in and let nature take its course. Thats it.
我的工作是在为你带来，让顺其自然。这就是它。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Hey, I got a GPS on the phone. He's heading North. You want me to send units?
嘿，我得到了手机上的GPS。他向北。你要我送单位？
Don't bother. He's gone.
不要打扰。他走了。
-Dead end. -Wait, wait.
-Dead结束。 - 等待，等待。
-He wants us to watch it. -Why?
- 他要我们看它。 - 为什么？
I don't know yet.
我还不知道。
Who she waiting for?
谁让她还在等什么？
Who are these guys?!
这些家伙是谁？！
Holy shit!
神圣的狗屎！
Get me a tech guy. I need some magic done on a security tape, now. Right now!
给我一个高科技的家伙。我需要一些魔术做一个安全的磁带，现在。现在！
Hey, let me guess.
嘿，让我猜。
Pile up on the 710N
堆积在710N
massive cluster of police vehicles 15 miles heading south
警车大规模集群15英里向南
Sounds about right.
声音对的。
Hey, thanks Sam.
嘿，感谢萨姆。
You want to tell me what's going on?
你要告诉我这是怎么回事？
Lenore sent me a text.
勒诺给我发了一个文本。
Asked to come over to my place for bagels.
问过来到我的地方百吉饼。
I got the bagels.
我得到的面包圈。
When I came back, I found her car out front.
当我回来的时候，我发现她的车出门前。
and
和
she was in my bed with her throat slashed.
，她在我的床上，她的喉咙削减。
Oh Jesus.
哦耶稣。
What else?
还有什么呢？
I found a location on her car's GPS from the night before.
我发现她的汽车的前一天晚上从GPS的位置。
She was out of this gas station in the middle of nowhere
她出这个加油站在不着村后不着
I saw it on the security camera
我看到了它的安全性相机
She was snatched.
，她被抢走。
What do you want us to do?
你要什么我们做什么？
I downloaded all the phone records from the police files. I'm on it.
我下载了警方文件中的所有通话记录。我就可以了。
Maybe there's something there.
也许有什么东西在那里。
I didn't notice that this
，我没有注意到这
Her hair
她的头发
It might turn up something. It might turn up nothing.
这可能转起来的东西。它可能变成了什么。
Anything else?
还有别的吗？
I want to go to the funeral
我要去参加葬礼
The Bible constantly tells us
圣经不断的告诉我们，
that there will be difficult times in life.
，将有困难的时候在生活中。
When we feel like we are walking to a dark, dangerous valley.
当我们觉得我们是步行到一个黑暗，危险的山谷。
-Valley of the shadow of death. -Are you OK?
死亡的阴影-Valley。 -Are你确定？
But what the Word of God does make very clear
但是，什么神的话语确实让非常清楚
is that as we move through such times
是因为我们经历这样的时代
the LORD is my Shepard and He maketh me to lie down in green pastors
耶和华是我的谢泼德和他使我在绿色牧师躺下
He leadeth me besides still waters
他领我除了静水
In the name of the Father
在父亲的名称
and of the Son
子和
And of the Holy Spirit
圣灵和
you already know
您已经知道
Right there.
就在那里。
Get me sound on that.
给我的声音上。
Kim.
金。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
If there's anything we can do
如果有什么事我们可以做
Hey
嘿嘿
We're there for you. You know that, right?
我们在你身边。你知道，对吧？
Hey baby
嘿，宝贝
I just want to go home
我只是想回家
You hear that?
你听到了吗？
Hear the click?
听到的点击？
Yeah, I'm getting some interference somewhere.
是啊，我得到了一些干扰的地方。
He's gonna go to Kim now
他会去金现在
-Hey -Hi
- 嘿嗨
Oh sweetie
哦，亲爱的
They're jamming our signal
他们干扰我们的信号
I know
我知道
I'm so, so sorry
，我非常，非常抱歉
Listen
收听
He'll be in touch
，他会和你联系
just stick to your schedule
只是坚持你的日程安排
Your very predictable schedule
您非常可预测的时间表
You want me to put a tail on him?
你要我把尾巴上他？
Nah, it's a waste of time. They're always about winning
不，这是在浪费时间。他们总是赢球
These guys could lose a tail if it was attached to a dog
这些家伙可以，如果它是附着在狗失去了尾巴
We're done.
，我们就大功告成了。
Cut the feed
切料
Stuart, why are there still
斯图尔特，​​为何仍有
Why are there still cops camped outside?
为何仍有警察外安营扎寨？
Uh, I think it's just standard operating procedure.
嗯，我认为这只是标准作业程序。
What do you think my dad is gonna show up here?
你觉得我爸是会出现在这里？
Are they stupid or something?
他们是不是有点傻？
I don't know what they think.
我不知道他们怎么想。
Inspector Dotzler asked if we minded and I said no
督察Dotzler向您问我们是否介意和我说没有
You should have asked me.
你应该问我。
I mind
我介意
I'm sorry
对不起
And who's he?
，谁是他？
Well, we um...
好吧，我们嗯...
we need protection
，我们需要保护
Kim, honey, I know it's hard on you but it's hard on me, too.
金，亲爱的，我知道这很难对你，但它很难对我了。
I'm sorry I didn't realize it was a competition
对不起我不知道这是一个竞争
It's...
这是...
it's not a competition, please.
这不是比赛，请。
Don't hate me
不要恨我
I'm not responsible for what happen
我不负责什么发生
I don't hate you, Stuart
我不恨你，斯图尔特
But for the last 2 years
，但在过去的2年
every time I looked into my mom's eyes the only thing I saw was hurt and sadness
每次我看着妈妈的眼睛时，我看到的唯一的事情是真的在痛，悲伤
And for that, I do hold you responsible
而对于这一点，我就抱着你负责
-Where're you going? -School
-Where're你要去？ - 学生
If I'm allowed
如果我让
Why are you following me?
你为什么跟着我？
It's for your own protection, miss.
这是为自己的保护，小姐。
Protection?
保护？
From who?
从谁？
My father?
我的父亲？
You really think my father would hurt me?
你真的认为我父亲会伤害我吗？
Your mother probably didn't think so either
你妈妈可能没想到，所以无论是
Asshole
混蛋
-Hi -Hey
嗨 - 嘿
Drink me now
现在喝我
Anything?
什么？
She's on campus. You want me to follow?
她是在校园里。你要我跟着？
Is the bug active?
是错误主动？
Yes.
是
OK, stay near her
OK，留在她身边
Really soon. If he shows up we're here
真的很快。如果他显示了我们在这里
What else?
还有什么呢？
She went to this convenient store and chugged
她去这家便利商店，喝着
down a drink of some kind from the fridge
下跌某种从冰箱里饮料
Uh huh
嗯
Was it skinny or fat?
是不是瘦还是胖？
As you might remember last week
正如你可能还记得，上周
We discussed dissociation and interactions between
我们讨论解离和之间的相互作用
dorsal and ventral streams in object recognition...
背和物体识别腹侧流...
Is that the dorsal stream is supporting motor interactions with objects
是背流支持与物体运动的相互作用
while ventral streams structures extract visual
，而腹侧流结构中提取视觉
information about the object that is independent
约是独立对象的信息
I'm feeling a bit nauseous
我感觉有点恶心
-Can you right the notes for me? -Yeah, sure
- 你能适合我的笔记？是啊，肯定
Thanks
感谢
Now in other words, object knowledge is represented in ventral streams
现在，换句话说，对象的知识被表示在腹侧流
Excuse me, I wonder if you could help me out with something.
对不起，我不知道如果你能帮助我的东西。
Sure
确定
There was a young women in here. About an hour ago
有一个女青年在这里。大约一个小时前
Oh yeah
哦
Poor kid
可怜的孩子
She come here often?
，她经常到这里来？
Everyday
每天
-She bought when? -Same thing. Peach, yogurt, drink
- 她买的是什么时候？ -Same的事情。桃子，酸奶，喝
But today, she drank it all right there from the fridge
但今天，她喝了这一切在那里从冰箱里
Must have been thirsty
必须一直渴
Get anything?
获取什么？
Yeah, she went to school. Got nauseous in class
是啊，她去学校。在课堂上感到恶心
Now she's on her way to the bathroom
现在，她是在她的途中上厕所
Call for back up! I'm coming right now!
征集回来了！我马上来！
Shh
嘘
Here Kim, drink this. I put something in the yogurt to make you nauseous
这里金，喝这个。我把东西在酸奶让你恶心
this will take it away
，这将带走吧
Hi baby
宝宝喜
Hi
喜
Oh Kimmy
哦吉米
Oh Kim
呵呵金
Dad
爸爸
I don't know what to do
，我不知道该怎么办
I'm pregnant
我怀孕了
What?
什么？
Dad
爸爸
I'm OK
我OK
I have low blood sugar. I haven't eaten since yesterday
我有低血糖。我从昨天起还没有吃
Eat this
吃这个
Don't, don't you worry
不要，你不要担心
Lets get through this first, and then we'll figure out what's best for
让我们通过这个先得到，然后我们会找出最适合
What you have to do, Kim, is act natural. This cop is really smart.
，你所要做的，金，就是行动自然。这是警察真的聪明。
Anything out of the usual he becomes suspicious, OK?
任何不平常，他变得疑神疑鬼，OK？的
I love you
我爱你
I love you, too
我爱你，太
Yes?
是？
Where are you?
你在哪里？
I'm in the science building east left
我在科学楼东侧离开
-She's in the bathroom. -Don't move.
- 她在浴室里。 - 不要动。
Wait for me.
等我。
Where are you staying?
你在哪里住？
I'm still at mom's
我还是在妈妈的
I started packing her stuff
我开始收拾她的东西
it just...
，它只是...
it doesn't feel real
不会感到真正的
Oh I know
哦，我知道，
I know
我知道
Dad there's...
爸爸有...
Stuarts been acting really weird
斯图亚特已经演技确实很奇怪，
He must be scared about something. He hired body guards.
他一定是害怕的东西。他雇了保镖。
Oh my God it was so fun. But you know what he was such a jerk
噢，我的上帝，它是如此有趣。但你知道他是这样的混蛋
Really?
真的吗？
He made me pay for my own drink at the bar
他让我在酒吧支付自己的饮料
I did! I was wearing something like more skimpier than this
我做到了！我穿着像比这更多skimpier
Really? More skimpier than that?
真的吗？比这更skimpier？
They'll hear you
他们会听你的
I'm not gonna do it again there.
我不会再做一次出现。
I completely understand
我完全理解
Oh!
哦！
Move, move, move, move, move
移动，移动，移动，移动，移动
Excuse me!
对不起！
Perv!
首页上一页！
He just left.
他刚离开。
She's in the can.
她在可以的。
I can't let you leave.
，我不能让你离开。
Seal entrances
密封入口
Hey!
嘿！
There he is.
他在那里。
Gotta stop the water!
住手水！
Freeze!
不许动！
I know you think your helping him.
我知道你觉得你在帮他。
But your not
，但你不能
Your not.
您没有。
This we can't recommend
此，我们不建议
I can't start trying to make sense of what happened
我无法启动试图使发生了什么意义
Someone killed my mom.
有人杀了我妈妈。
That's what happen
这就是发生
It was not my father
这不是我的父亲
We haven't heard his side of the story
我们没有听到他身边的故事
They can't know that can they?
他们不能知道他们能？
I do.
我做的。
Is there anything else?
还有什么？
You know we can arrest you for obstructing an ongoing investigation.
你知道我们可以逮捕你阻挠正在进行的调查。
Arrest me.
逮捕我。
I rather not.
我宁可不要。
Well then, If your not going to
那么，如果你不打算
can I go home?
我可以回家了？
Course.
课程。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Interesting family
有趣的家庭
Don't worry.
不要担心。
We will take care of this.
我们将利用这一服务。
Do as we planned.
难道是我们的计划。
Call the car
通话汽车
Where are we going boss?
我们去哪儿的老板？
Malibu house.
马里布的房子。
Okay, lets go get drunk.
好了，让我们去喝醉。
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我不会伤害你。
I need a ride.
，我需要一程。
-Mind if i drive? -OK.
-Mind如果我开车吗？ -OK。
You can go.
你可以走了。
Uh huh
嗯
You when you stand in the field with a box of matches.
你当你站在现场用一盒火柴。
You can have hundreds of rabbits in seconds like this
您可以有数百个兔子在几秒钟内像这样
-You know how? -No.
- 你知道怎么样？ -No。
Come in all rabbits
进来所有的兔子
Like this
像这样
Who hired you?
谁雇你？
Huh!
呵呵！
Who are you working for?
你是谁工作？
Your accent is shit!
你的口音是狗屎！
I'd rather die than tell you!
我宁可死也不告诉你！
Boss, they're at the gate.
老大，他们在大门口。
Well let them in.
好让他们在
Oh, and take a stroll. I need a little privacy.
哦，散步。我需要一点点的隐私。
Manny?
曼尼？
Manny!?
曼尼！？
Bryan.
布莱恩。
Oh, God no, please!
哦，上帝没有，请！
None of this is making any sense to me, Stuart.
没有这使得任何意义，我，斯图尔特。
I was hoping you could help me out.
我希望你能帮助我。
How did you...
你是如何...
Survive the crash?
生存崩溃？
The Russians who were following me when I was following you
，当我跟随你谁是跟着我的俄罗斯
-They work for you, Stuart? -No.
你  - 它们的工作，斯图尔特？ -No。
I don't know what your talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
What do you know!
你知道些什么！
The only thing I know is that you were screwing my wife.
我知道的唯一的事情是，你拧我的妻子。
And I know that she's dead
，我知道她已经死了
No! No! Not...
不！不！不...
What do you know!
你知道些什么！
I don't know anything
我不知道什么
I swear I don't know anything.
我发誓，我什么都不知道。
If I believed that, we wouldn't be here!
如果我认为，我们不会在这里！
No! No! No!!!!
不！不！无!!!!
What!?
什么！？
Malankov
Malankov
Oleg Malankov
奥列格Malankov
-Who is Oleg Malankov? -I owe him money.
- 谁是奥列格Malankov？ -I欠他的钱。
You don't know him. He will never give up.
你不认识他。他绝不会放弃。
Its only a game for him.
它只是一个游戏了。
I lost everything
我失去了一切
-He said he'd kill my family -Why didn't you tell this to the police?
- 他说他会杀了我的家人 - 为什么不告诉这个警察？
You let them think it was me.
你让他们觉得这是我的。
I was angry with you God damn it. You promised, you promised to stop seeing her.
我很生气，你他妈的。你答应了，你答应不再见她。
So what do you think happen?
所以，你觉得怎样？
She came over to my place. This Malankov followed her there
她走过来我的地方。这Malankov跟着她有
If you weren't seeing her being my back, she wouldn't
如果你没有看到她是我的背，她不会
have been there in the first place, would she?
已经在第一时间在那里，她会？
They would have killed her someplace else.
，他们会杀了她别的地方。
So why are they coming after me?
那么，为什么他们后，我来了？
Because I told them who you were
因为我告诉他们你是谁
That you would find them and kill them.
，你会发现他们并杀死他们。
How convenient would that be for you.
如何方便的将是对你。
I kill them. Your debt is canceled.
我杀了他们。你的债务被取消。
I'm sorry, Bryan.
对不起，布莱恩。
But I loved her. You gotta believe me. I loved her, I loved her.
但是我爱她。你得相信我。我爱她，我爱她。
Well, here's what your gonna do.
好了，这里就是你该怎么办。
Your gonna go to the police and tell them everything
你会去报警，告诉他们一切
I can't
我不能
I can't. He's crazy. You don't know him. You can do whatever you want.
我不能。他是疯了。你不认识他。你可以做任何你想要的。
Either way, I'm a dead man.
无论哪种方式，我就死定了。
I'm dead.
我已经死了。
They kill you, they don't get paid.
，他们杀了你，他们没有得到报酬。
Your not the one they're gonna come after next.
您不是一个他们会来后，下一个。
Kim.
金。
Hey!
嘿！
Can you get your keys, please?
，你可以得到你的钥匙吗？
Do you know what your getting yourself into,
你知道你得到自己陷入，
man?
男人？
Yes, as a matter of fact, I do. Could you get your keys and your phone, please?
是的，事实上，我这样做。你可以让你的钥匙和手机，请？
you mind putting your hand on the steering wheel?
你介意把你的手放在方向盘上？
Or what?
还是什么？
What are you gonna do? Shoot me?
你打算怎么办？拍我？
Left or right?
左边还是右边？
Go ahead, put the cuffs on.
来吧，把袖口上。
Thank you very much.
非常感谢你。
Dad!?
爸爸！？
Lets go Kim.
让我们去金。
-Whats going on? -I'm keeping you safe.
-Whats怎么回事？ -I'm保持你的安全。
Sam?
山姆？
Hey, Kim.
嘿，金。
We're gonna get in the truck
我们在卡车谈婚论嫁
Hi Kim!
喜金！
Lets go
让我们去
Dotzler
多兹勒
Garcia and his team were just attack by Mills!
加西亚和他的团队只是米尔斯攻击！
What?
什么？
He took the daughter out of St. John's house.
他把女儿带出的圣约翰的家。
Fucking sake, man!
他妈的的缘故，男人！
I'll be there right away
我会在那里马上
-Anything yet? -No
-Anything了吗？ -No
Nothing came up from the samples you gave me, but
没有从样本来到了你给我的，但
it's gonna take a while to sort through, Bryan. There's a shit load of data here
它会需要一段时间才能通过排序，布莱恩。有数据狗屎负荷这里
What is that?
那是什么？
I downloaded the police computers.
我下载了警察的电脑。
For what?
为了什么？
First thing they're going to look at are the phone records to see if there are any clues.
他们会看的第一件事是电话记录，看看是否有任何的线索。
Mine and Lenore's.
矿山和勒诺的。
I mean what's it gonna tell ya?
我的意思是什么它会告诉你？
That you and Lenore spoke to each other?
，你和勒诺说话对方？
Hey, you know what? Don't worry about it anyway. We're almost done here anyway.
嘿，你知道吗？不要担心也无妨。我们几乎在这里完成而已。
So what's the plan?
那么，有什么计划？
The plan is to make sure my daughter safe.
的计划是要确保我女儿的安全。
And the only way to do that, so it seems, is to
要做到这一点的唯一途径，如此看来，是
eliminate the thing that would make her unsafe
消除，这将使她的不安全的东西
-Malankov. -Good one, Stuart
-Malankov。 - 良好之一，斯图尔特
I'd like to help
我想帮助
Oh your gonna help, alright.
哦，你要去帮忙，没事的。
Like bait helps to catch a shark
就像诱饵有助于捕捉鲨鱼
Excuse me?
对不起？
Start talking about Malankov.
开始谈论Malankov。
I want to know every detail.
我想知道每一个细节。
Who he is
他是谁
What he does
，他能做什么
Where he lives.
他住哪儿，
Where he works.
在哪里，他的作品。
Oleg Malankov
奥列格Malankov
He's as tough as they come
，因为他们来他的强硬
He served in the Russian army when they invaded Afghanistan
他曾在俄罗斯军队时，他们入侵阿富汗
He was Spetnaz
他Spetnaz
It's like our Navy Seals.
这就像我们的海豹突击队。
After the collapse of the Soviet Union, when everyone was grabbing what they could
苏联解体后，在大家揪着自己能否
there was a real demand for men with his kind of skills
有男性，他种的技能真正需求
He become one of the grabbers
他成为掠夺者之一
I met him when I was doing a deal involving heavy machinery
我见到他时，我在做涉及重型机械的交易
Since then, we did business in a number of different occasions
此后，我们在许多不同的场合所做的公​​司
Some deals worked out
一些交易制定了
I don't have the money
我没有钱
Last one didn't
最后一个没
What?
什么？
My mom is dead because of one of your shitty business deals?
我的妈妈死了，因为你的低劣的生意呢？
No, no, no, Kim. That's not what happen
不，不，不，金。这不是发生
I knew it!
我就知道！
-Let me go! -Kim.
- 让我走！ -Kim。
-It's his fault. He killed her!
- 它是他的错。他杀死了她！ -Kim。
He killed her!
他杀害了她！
We need him.
我们需要他。
Call him.
打电话给他。
-Why? -Because your gonna set him up for me.
- 为什么？ - 因为你要去把他为我说话。
Make the call, now!
拨打电话，现在！
On speaker
打开扬声器
Stuart
斯图尔特
I've missed you.
我已经错过了你。
I have your money
我有你的钱
You have it?
你有吗？
That was fast.
那是快的。
How can I trust you?
我怎么能相信你吗？
You can trust me
你可以相信我
Where'd you want me to bring it?
哪儿你要我把它？
Meet me at the building down town.
认识我在大楼进城。
In about 1 hour.
在约1小时。
Sure, 1 hour
当然，1小时
Scumbag
卑鄙小人
Tell me how security works
告诉我如何安全工程
Malankov
Malankov
He works out of his penthouse apartment
他的作品从他的复式公寓
He has a private elevator with 2 body guards
他与2保镖私人电梯
The elevators is controlled by security upstairs.
的电梯被保安上楼控制。
Once they see who's inside the elevator and give the OK
一旦他们看看谁的电梯内，给予确定
they'll send the elevator up
，他们会送电梯上去
outside the elevator upstairs is the security station and 3 more body guards
外的电梯上楼是安全站和3个保镖
2 sets of doors
2套门
through the second set of doors is Malankov's private apartment
通过第二组门是Malankov的私人公寓
Hey, can you help me out here?
嘿，你能不能帮我在这里？
I've got an address but I don't have a name
我有一个地址，但我没有名字
And I got a back full of perishables.
，我得到了一回全易腐的。
Go to the first floor and ask for the desk, alright?
转到一楼，并要求在桌子，好吗？
First floor? Thank you so much
一楼？太谢谢你了
You welcome.
您的欢迎。
-Hello sir. -I'm here to see Oleg Malankov
- 你好，先生。 -I'm这里看看奥列格Malankov
OK sir, have a good day
OK先生，有一个美好的一天
Thanks
感谢
Get out
滚出
It's Dotzler
这是多兹勒
Answer it. Act normal.
答案吧。行动正常。
Don't try anything smart
不要尝试任何聪明
-Hello. -Mr. St. John, Frank Dotzler
- 你好。 -先生。圣约翰，弗兰克·多兹勒
Where are you?
你在哪里？
I'm at a business meeting. Is there anything wrong?
我在一个商务会议。有什么错吗？
Bryan Mills remove your step daughter from your home
布赖恩·米尔斯从你家中删除您的女儿步
I'm here right now
我在这里现在
-Oh my God. That's um... -When are you coming home?
- 哦，我的上帝。这嗯...  - 当你什么时候回家？
Well, I'm leaving immediately it should take
好吧，我马上离开，应该采取
me about an hour to get there from where I am
我约一个小时，从那里我那里
Where exactly is that?
具体在哪里呢？
In Malibu. Listen inspector, I don't think he means her any harm. He's...
在马里布。听检查，我不认为他的意思是她造成任何伤害。他...
Mr. St. john
先生。圣约翰
this man is the prime suspect in the murder of your wife!
这个人是你的妻子的谋杀案的主要嫌疑人！
His associated have guns on my men in the front of your home
有关他有枪我的男人在你家门前
As far as I'm concern, he's dangerous and has to be taken into custody
至于我的关注，他的危险并已被收押
So if you'd like, I can send a car for you but I need you somewhere safe
所以，如果你愿意，我可以派车给你，但我需要你安全的地方
No, no, no, no, no, no,it's fine. I'm uh..
不，不，不，不，不，不，它的罚款。我呃..
I'm leaving right now
我要离开现在
I'll be waiting for you
我会等着你
Get me a location on St. John's phone
给我一个位置，在圣约翰的电话
As soon as he finds out your not in Malibu
一旦他发现你不是在马里布
he'll be headed right here
，他会在这里当家
I'd say we um less than thirty minutes to do this before he shows up
我会说，我们呃不到三十分钟就做到这一点之前，他展示了
That's enough time for me
这是有足够的时间对我来说
Can you handle this, Kim?
你能解决这个问题，金？
What do I have to do?
我有什么做的？
Just keep me up to date. Whatever comes up
只是让我一直保持最新状态。无论发生什么事了
Thanks, Sam
谢谢，山姆
Inspector
督察
Tape you gave us of the gas station. These are stills. Frame by frame
带你给加油站的我们。这些剧照。一帧一帧
Hey, he lied to you about where he was
哎，他骗了你在哪里，他是
What a surprise
什么惊喜
-He's down town. -lets go get the calvary
- 他的进城。 - 允许去拿各各
Alright
好吧
Found his location. We're on the move.
找到了自己的位置。我们在移动。
Lets go!
让我们去！
They're gone
他们走了
OK.
确定。
-Cops on the move. -OK.
-Cops上移。 -OK。
lets go
让我们去
You do exactly as you were told. Don't improvise
你做的完全一样，你被告知。不要凑合
Try anything funny and they'll kill you
尝试有趣的东西，他们会杀了你
And if they don't, I will
如果他们不这样做，我会
I don't know how many times I can say sorry
我不知道有多少次我可以说对不起，
Come here, Kim
来到这里，金
Here
这里
Dotzler
多兹勒
I found out something you might wanna know
，我发现了一些东西，你可能想知道
matching insurance policies on St. John's wife
在圣约翰的妻子匹配保险
twelve million each
12000000每个
How bout that?
如何回合呢？
Stuart St. John. Mr. Malankov is expecting me
斯图亚特·圣约翰。 Malankov先生等着我
What's in the bag?
什么是收入囊中？
We're in
我们在
Alright, OK.
好了，OK。
Stuart St. John is clear
斯图亚特·圣·约翰是明确
Unlock the elevator
打开电梯
OK.
确定。
Got em
得到了EM
Go! Alright.
去！好吧。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Everything OK?
一切OK？
Call the elevator
呼叫电梯
Get back to the truck
找回卡车
Bingo!
宾果！
Right on
右键在
He's coming now
，他的到来，现在
Go, go, go, go, go ,go
走，走，走，走，走，走
Show time
显示时间
bingo
宾果
What the hell is going on?
这到底是怎么回事？
guys?
家伙？
Go check it out
去看看
Get up
起床
Get up!
起来！
Who are you old man?
你是谁老头？
You killed my ex wife!
你杀了我的前妻！
But your not gonna kill my daughter!
但你不是要杀了我女儿！
Your daughter?
你的女儿？
Shit!
妈的！
We're fucked by the same man
我们被同一个男人性交
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Stuart St. John
斯图亚特·圣约翰
First he gets me to kill your wife, then you
首先，他得到了我要杀死你的妻子，那么你
And then that doesn't work. He puts you to kill me
然后不起作用。他把你杀了我
Either way he wins
不管怎样他赢了
Your wife
你老婆
was just part of a business deal
是一宗商业交易的一部份
Like many before
像许多前
it's my turn to lose the game
轮到我输掉比赛
Finish me!
完成了我！
I deserve it!
我活该！
Yes
是
You do.
你做的。
Need to see you. Meet me at the Rancho Berrego. Bryan
需要见你。迎接我的牧场Berrego。布莱恩
Text from your phone asking mom to meet you at the rancho
问妈妈见到你的牧场，从您的手机文本
Berrego the night she died. someone used your phone
Berrego她死了一夜。有人用你的电话
Dad
爸爸
listen
听
-Dad -What is it?
-Dad  - 什么是什么呢？
Dad! Dad!
爸爸！爸爸！
Kim!
金！
Come on, lets go. lets go
来吧，让我们去。让我们去
Get in the car!
上车！
Lets go, come on!
让去，加油！
Where are we going?
我们要去哪里？
Get in the car
上车
He's still alive. Lets get a medic in here. ASAP medic
，他还活着。让我们得到一个军医在这里。尽快军医
Inspector the elevator
督察电梯
Dotzler, It's Smith
Dotzler向您，这是史密斯
We're in Malankov's building I think Mills is here.
我们在Malankov的建设，我认为米尔斯是在这里。
-Really? -Yeah, I'm gonna check the apartment now
- 真的？是啊，我要立即检查公寓
Back it up. back it up.
备份。备份。
Alright, lets go. Everybody in.
好吧，让我们去。每个人都英寸
Come on, lets go!
来吧，让我们去！
We got a good chance he's still in the building. Call down stairs. Lock it up!
我们得到了一个很好的机会，他仍然在建设。呼叫上下楼梯。锁起来！
Nobody in, nobody out
没人，也没人出来
Lock it out. Nobody in, nobody out
锁定它。没有人，没有人出来
Text from your from asking to meet you at the
从询问，以满足您的 正文从
ranch the night she died. Someone used your phone
牧场她死了一夜。有人用你的手机
Tracking Kim cell
跟踪金正日细胞
Hey! who's in there!
嘿！谁在那里！
Santa Monica aviation. This is Mrs. ST. John I'll be
圣莫尼卡航空。这是ST夫人。约翰我会
there in 15 minutes. Get the plane ready. It will be ready
在15分钟内出现。获取飞机准备。这将准备
Why are you doing this?
你为什么要这么做？
Because your father and his friends are homicidal maniacs
因为你的父亲和他的朋友们杀人的疯子
Your a lying piece of shit
您一个躺在一块狗屎
Shut up -
闭嘴 -
You killed her I know it -Shut up
你杀了她，我知道闭嘴
You Shut up!
你闭嘴！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
Brooks
布鲁克斯
I want you to look up for a black Porsche license plate number 689MJC6
我要你看看了一个黑色的保时捷车牌号689MJC6
OK
OK
Connect to the Porsche when we trace it!
连接到保时捷的时候，我们跟踪它！
Alright
好吧
I need a run on a California plate 689-Mary- Jane- Charlie-6
我需要在加州板运行689  - 玛丽 -  Jane-查理-6
I need a phone, too
，我需要一个电话，过
Incoming call... Unknown
来电...未知
Pick up the phone
拿起电话
Black Porsche just spotted heading West
黑色保时捷只是看上往西
Yes.
是
Listen, Mr. Mills. It's Dotzler
听着，米尔斯先生。这是Dotzler向您
I still have to piece this thing together
我还是要拼凑这个东西在一起
There's two life insurance policies
有两种生命保险
One for St. John. One for your ex wife, you understand?
一为圣约翰。一个是你的前妻，你明白吗？
Stuart owed money to these Russians. A lot of it.
司徒拖欠货款这些俄罗斯人。很多吧。
The ones who abducted her
谁绑架她的人
The men then took her to my place to kill her to keep me out of the way
男人然后把她带到我家来杀她让我闪开
I need you to step back and allow me to handle this
我需要你退后一步，让我来处理这个
I got it
我得到了它
What's your first priority here, inspector?
什么是你的首要位置，督察？
To arrest St. John and charge him with your ex wife's murder
要逮捕圣约翰，并指控他与你的前妻的谋杀
My first priority is my daughter
我的首要任务是我的女儿
Get out of the car
下车的
Come on, lets go
来吧，让我们去
Go!
去！
Kim's cell Santa Monica airport
金正日的细胞圣莫尼卡机场
OK, we're leaving now
OK，我们要离开现在
-Come on, lets go. -Yes, sir.
-COMe上，让我们去。 - 是的，先生。
Requesting clear for take off
请求明确的起飞
Come on, guys. Come on, lets go
来吧，伙计们。来吧，让我们去
Requesting permission for take off
请求允许起飞
We got a visual on the Porsche
我们得到了一个视觉上的保时捷
He's heading to Santa Monica Airport
他前往圣莫尼卡机场
I want all units in the area of the Santa Monica
我想在圣莫尼卡的区域中的所有单元
airport to be on the look out for a black Porsche
机场是在寻找一个黑色保时捷
89-90
89-90
No
否
Lets go, lets go!
让我们走，让我们去！
Come on!
加油！
Go!
去！
Give me the God damn gun!
给我该死的枪！
Shoot you in the head!
拍你的头！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
Very smart.
非常聪明。
Played me off against the Russians
玩过我了反对俄国
Coming over for coffee
即将在咖啡
Taking my phone, sending text, and then erasing them!
以我的电话，发送文本，然后将其删除！
So that your pals could plant Lenore's body and make it look as if I killed her
那么，你的好朋友可以种植勒诺的身体，使它看起来好像是我杀了她
Well your problem solved
嗯，你的问题就解决了​​
All your worries over
您所有的忧虑
But it didn't quit work out that way
，但它并没有停止工作了这样
Listen, Bryan
听，布莱恩
They're coming
他们来了
You can't kill me now
你不能杀我现在
Oh yeah?
哦？
Dad.
爸爸。
I know you know alot of people
我知道你知道很多人
and with a good lawyer you'll get out of jail in a few years
，并与一个好律师，你会走出监狱的几年
and then I'll come for you
，然后我就来为你
I'll find you
我会找到你
And we both know what's gonna happen
，我们都知道什么是要发生的事
I knew from the beginning
，我从一开始就知道
It was the bagels
这是百吉饼
They were warm
他们温暖
I mean I had to ask myself what kind of guy
我的意思是，我不得不问自己是什么样的人
goes out for warm bagels
熄灭温暖的百吉饼
and comes back and commits a murder?
，回来和犯了谋杀罪？
So, I compared
所以，我比较
the time stamps to the deleted texts
时间戳来删除文本
That you downloaded from our computers
，你从我们的电脑下载
which by the way is illegal
它的方式是非法的
and we could arrest you for it
，我们可以抓你为它
either way, I could
无论哪种方式，我可以
But it's got me
，但它让我
and I was able to figure it out
，我是能够弄明白
She was leaving him
她要离开他
He needed the insurance money to pay Malankov
他需要的保险金支付Malankov
you didn't help us out by escaping you
你没有帮助我们通过逃避你
You figured what better way to get rid of Malankov and keep the insurance money
你想出什么更好的办法来摆脱Malankov和保持保险金
than by getting me the kill the guy who would kill him
不是让我杀了谁也杀了他的家伙
because it was the only way to keep my daughter safe
，因为它是让我的女儿安全的唯一方法
It almost worked
它几乎工作
Almost
几乎
So, are we done, Inspector?
所以，我们都做了，督察？
Course
课程
course
当然
We're done
，我们就大功告成了
Could you um, just stay in town for the next month or
你能不能嗯，只是停留在镇为下个月
so. Just in case I have a few other questions for you
等。以防万一我有几个问题要问你
Sure.
当然，
Now you two
现在你们两个
I've though about this all night
我有，虽然这一切晚上
It's um...
这嗯...
very important choice
非常重要的选择
whatever you decide
无论你决定
the two of you
你们两个
together
一起
I'll support you 100%
我支持你100％
And I know your mom would have said the same thing too
我知道你妈妈会说同样的事情太多
Tell em
告诉他们
Dad
爸爸
We've been talking
我们一直在谈论
We though that
我们尽管这
If it's a girl,
如果它是一个女孩，
we'd like to name her after mom
我们想妈妈后，她的名字
She'd like that very much, Kim.
她想了很多，金。